Finding Aid for the Allegra Fuller Snyder papers, 1960-2010 LSC.1881
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Personal Organizational Files, 1960-2010
  - Scott Rosalsky, Marion-Spirit Dances (2 of 2)., 2002-2004 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    Rehearsal notes. Correspondence. Newsclippings.
  - Seidel, Andrea Mantell., 1994-2003 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    "Isadora Duncan Dance Ensemble" brochures. CVs. Proposal "Dancing Across Disciplines: an alliance between area studies and dance in the intercultural community." "The Intercultural Challenge in Teaching Dance History: a new paradigm for the 21st century." Correspondence.
  - Seidel, Andrea Mantell-Florida International University., 1991-2007 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    Letter of recommendation. Intercultural Dance Institute 1991 project description and lecture series spring 1992. FIU student handbook for dance majors. Correspondence. FIU packet. "Miss Asian American Florida Pageant and Cultural Showcase" program for 1991. Summer 1991 "Hemisphere: A magazine of Latin American and Caribbean Affairs." "FIU Festival of Dance 1992" poster. FIU performance programs.
  - Seldes, Marian., 2000-2007 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    Photocopied newsclippings.
  - Sellars, Peter., 1989-1990 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Sengekontacket Pond Watershed., undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
    Informational letter.
  - Shah, Purnima., 1991 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    Letters regarding her study of dance ethnology.
  - Shapiro, Florence Ida Snyder., 2006 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    AFS's sister-in-law's obituary.
  - Sharma, Aparna., 2007 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    AFS letter about film being the literature of dance.
  - Shearer, Sybil., 2005 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Sheldrake, Rupert., 1983 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    March "Investigations: A bulletin of the human consciousness research program."
  - Sherman, Lee., 1998 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Shimin, Tonia., 1995-2006 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    "Mary Anthony: A life in modern dance" project. Anthony documentary rough cut for scenes, treatments, brochures. Correspondence. CV.
  - Shur, Fanchon., 1986-2004 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    "Growth in Motion Center" brochures, flyers. "Taalit: Prayer shawl" program and photos. "Growth in Motion Celebrating 25 Years" brochures. "Flight, Fight, Freeze!" brochures and flyer.
  - Siegel, Marcia B., 1983-1998 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    "Dancing the Rage." Correspondence. Letters of recommendation. CVs. "Evolutionary Dreams Meredith Monk." "Carabosse in a Cocktail Dress." "Thirty Years in Eden's Dustbin." "Kabuki for Beginners." Book reviews. Course descriptions. "Shadows Past and Future." "Luminality in Balinese Dance."
  - Singer, Alice., 1968-1973 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    AFS letter announcing Singer's death. Project proposal for "Dance as Communication in the Culture of Macedonia."
  - Singha Reddy, Rina., 1977 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    Solo Recitals brochure. Photocopy of "Dancer Teaches Folklore to the Deaf" article. "Dancing Feet at Harbourfront's York Quay" flyer. CV. Letter.
  - Sklar, Deidre., 1985-2002 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    Letter of recommendation. "Can Bodylore Be Brought to Its Senses?" Course descriptions. CV. Letters of application to universities of dance teaching positions. Letters.
  - Skowhegan., 2003-2005 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Letter requesting permission to include Buckminster Fuller's lectures at the school of painting and sculpture as part of their archives.
  - Slavenska Corak, Mia., 2003-2007 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    "Mia: A dancer's Odyssey" trailer disc, postcards, statements by Slavenska Dance Preservation. Obituary. Memorial program. "A Dancer's Odyssey: The exile and return of Mia Slavenska" documentary statement.
  - Smith, Nancy R., 1987-1990 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    5 b/w photos of Smith taken by Lois Lord. The Center for Children program description. Letters from The Center for Children.
  - Smith, Phylise., 1989-1991 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    Letter of recommendation. Project Match. CV.
  - Smith, Richard Candida., 1988-1995 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    "Utopia and Dissent: Art, poetry, and politics in California" invitation for publication reception. "Popular Memory and Oral Narratives: Liusa Passerini's reading of oral history interviews." "Exquisite Corpse: The sense of the past in oral histories with California artists." "Imitation and Invention: Tradition and the avant-garde in the work of two Jewish Émigré American artists."
  - Smith, Sally Lieberman., 1992-2008 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    Newsclippings, articles. Flyer for "Teach Me Different" PBS video. "The Power of the Arts" invitation at The Lab School of Washington. Memorial notices. Obituary. Fall 2000, fall 2006, spring 2008 "The Lab School Link."
  - Snelson, Kenneth., 1990-2003 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    Letter. Exhibit notification cards.
  - Soleri, Paolo-Arcosanti., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    1994 "Arcommunique." 1995 Arcosanti course listings.
  - Somatics., 2002-2003 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    Conference on Somatics-defined as 'the body as experienced from within.' 2002 "Journal of Dance Education."
  - Somville, Marilyn Feller., 1991 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Sonnabend, Michael., 2000 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    AFS letter to Sonny about "Michelangelo: Self-Portrait" documentary.
  - Sorell, Walter., 1997 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Souriau, Manon., 1984 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    Letter regarding American Dance Guild.
  - Southern California Guild of Art Teachers (1 of 2)., 1967-1971 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    Membership lists. Pasadena Art Museum's choreographer's workshop. Marion Scott's "Contemporary Dance Production Inc NYC from '56-66 approx." NEA application for Choreographers Theatre for ChoreoConcerts. Long Beach Summer School of Dance 1970 catalog. NEA's "Annual Report 1969 The Arts." Nov. 1970, Jan. 1971 "The Circle: The official organ of the Creative Practices Council, Inc." Correspondence. Newsclippings, newsletters, bulletins and articles. Master classes by Bella Lewitzky Dance members. D.A.N.C.E. Dance Attractions for Nice Children Everywhere brochure.
  - Southern California Guild of Art Teachers (2 of 2)., 1968-1970 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Newsclippings. National Association for Regional Ballet's "Craft of Choreography Conferences" brochure and flyer. Alenikoff brochure. American School of Dance Scholarship Benefit invitation. Brochures and catalogs for dance programs offered throughout Southern California. Aman poster. Membership lists. Correspondence. 1968, 1969, 1971 ISOMATA catalogs.
  - Sparti, Barbara., 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    Correspondence about giving a joint presentation at 6th Conference of Association of European Dance Historians.
  - Spencer, Sam., undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
    Letter to AFS about Buckminster Fuller video.
  - Srinivasan, Ramesh., 2006 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    NEH fellowship application "Bridging Diaspora Via Cultural Information Systems." Letter of recommendation request.
  - Stark, Arlynne., 1984 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Stastny, Vera., 1994 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    Class lists.
  - St. Denis, Ruth., 1966 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    Photocopy of signed 1965 photo by Phil Baribault "The Spirit of Ruth St. Denis."
  - Steinberg, Saul., 1999 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Steinitz, Kate Trauman., 1976 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    Memorial exhibit invitation and works list. "Kate Steinitz Retrospective 1889-1975."
  - Steinway Family., 1979-1993 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    Newsclippings. Obituary of Elizabeth Steinway Chapin.
  - Stephens College., 1967-1969 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    "Appearance and Reality in the Film" four-weekend workshop at the Film Arts Theatre, Missouri. Film Institute brochures. Course outlines. Stephens College booklet and pack of postcards. Correspondence about a teaching position.
  - Steward, Jan., 1992 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    Thank you note to AFS. Book on Sister Corita Kent commentary.
  - Stifler, Sarah Lloyd., 1995 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    Letter and resume.
  - Stinson, Sue., undated (Box 28, Folder 18)
    Photocopy of page from "Funding for Museums, Archives and Special Collections."
  - Stoerchle, Carol Lingham., 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    Letter and article about memory of Wolfgang Stoerchle. List of friends and family.
  - Stoller, Roger W., 1999-2002 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    8x10 colored photo with sculpture. Letters and sculptures brochure.
  - Stover, Carl F., 1979 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    "The Practical Value of the Humanities and the Arts."
  - Streb, Elizabeth., 1997 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    "Tethering Newton's Apple to a Bungee Cord."
  - Stuart, Muriel., 1991 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    Davie Lerner and David Vaughan piece on Stuart's life for "Ballet Review."
  - Study Group on Ethnochoreology., 1994 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    1994 Study Group on Ethnochoreology minutes. Helene Eriksen brochure "Dances of the East."
  - Sturmer, Jerry., after 1995 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Summers, Elaine., 1992 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Kinetic Arts & Sciences letter. "MedArt International 1992 World Congress on Arts and Medicine."
  - Sun, Nilaja., 2006 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Article describing theatre "No Child."
  - Surrey University., 1986 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Undergraduate prospectus. Dance Conference and facilities appeal.
  - Susan Rose Dance Company., 1990-1994 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    Informational packet. CV.
  - Sussler, Ruth Lyford., 2000-2007 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    Postcards of Ruth and Albert Sussler art. Correspondence. Albert's resume.
  - Sussman, Deborah., 1998 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Sussman brochure. "Ray Kappe Awarded Distinguished Alumnus Medal."
  - Sweet, Jill D., 1990-2002 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    Skidmore College Native American Week program. NEH application "Dance of the San Juan Tewa Indians: Filming of movement studies." Grant application "Tourism and Tewa Indian Dance Events: A study in the cultural dynamics of Tewa/Anglo interactions."
  - Tara, Julie., undated (Box 29, Folder 10)
    Program for "The Goddess Descending."
  - Taylor, Paul., 1984, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    Articles.
  - Taymor, Julie., 1997 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    Tamara Geva obituary. Newsclippings.
  - Tennessee Children's Dance Ensemble., 1988 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Terry, Walter., 1947 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Tetley, Glen., 2007 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Twyla Tharp Dance., 1977, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    Newsclipping. "The Catherine Wheel" brochure.
  - Thomas, Katrina., undated (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Thompson, Robert., 1974 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    Jan.-Feb. "Media Matters."
  - Tipton, Gail., 1997 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Tolbert, Elizabeth (1 of 2)., 1988 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    PhD about the Karelian lament from Finland and Soviet Karelia.
  - Tolbert, Elizabeth (1 of 2)., 1988 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Tomkins, Calvin., 1991 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    AFS letter to possible Buckminster Fuller biographer.
  - Toumanova, Tamara., 1970 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    Sept. "Dance Magazine" article by Viola Hegyi Swisher.
  - Umatilla Indian Reservation., 1994 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    "Phases of the Umatilla Scalp Dance Project." Letters from Eliza Buck, Oregon Historical Society. NIPAD application "The Scalp Dance Project: A dance revitalization on the Umatilla Indian reservation."
  - University of Californian, Los Angeles (UCLA)-Current., 1993-1999 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    "Dance Under Construction: a brief history." Dance Dept. Self-review for Academic Senate. UCLA Center for Intercultural Performance fellowship applications. Correspondence about Pew Charitable Trust funding "UCLA National Dance/Media Project: Summary of leadership group thinking on public program initiatives." Save As: Dance brochure. Newsclippings. Asian Pacific Performance Exchange Program (APPEX) postcard. Letters about restructuring graduate schools. Winter 1996, winter 1997, spring 1998 "World Arts & Cultures Newsletter." Winter/Spring 1993 "ArtsWork." Spring 1997 "UCLA School of the Arts and Architecture Newsletter."
  - University of Californian, Los Angeles (UCLA)-Special Collections Dance Project., 2006-2010 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    Correspondence about AFS personal papers being brought to UCLA. "The Southern California Dance Legacy Project" description. List of other dance collection in UCLA Special Collections.
  - United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization (UNESCO) Project., 1993 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    William (Bill) Reynolds producing videos of traditional performing arts. Correspondence.
  - Vanammerkate, Gert-Jan., 1992 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Van Dobben, Danielle J., 2002 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - van Holt, Ynes., 2000-2002 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    "Tanzfabrik Berlin" program. Correspondence. "Essential Motion Work Process" holistic healing with dance. Some German texts.
  - Van Tine, Mary Pat., 1985 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    "Moving in Sound" brochure "The Healing Power of Movement Therapy."
  - Vatsyayan, Kapila., 1982-2004 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    Indira Gandhi National Centre for the Arts brochures. CV. Letter of recommendation. Observations of "UNESCO Workshop on Cross-Cultural Lifestyle Studies with Multimedia Computerisable Documentation." "Aesthetics in the Indian Arts" schedule for Vatsyayan at UCLA. Correspondence.
  - Villaella, Edward., 1988 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    Nov. 28 "Profiles II-The Prodigal" article.
  - Vischer, Joanna Brown., 1991-1999 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    Personal correspondence. 3 color photos.
  - Vouros, Mary., 1989 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    Letter about visits to Greece.
  - Wachsmann, Konrad., 1980 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    Obituary about the pioneer of prefabricated housing.
  - Walling, Savannah T. E., 1987 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    Research application "Sources: Study and research for 'A Gospel for Today'" including project description and resume. Prospectus for "Special Delivery Moving Theatre."
  - Warren, Nick., 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    Letter. CV. Description of "An Experimental Course on Perceptional Languages in Art and Science."
  - Washington, Lula., 2001 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    Photocopy of educator award announcement.
  - Waterman, Richard Alan., 1973 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    Alan Merriam's description of the ethnomusicologist's life.
  - Watts Towers and Film., 2006 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    Letters from Edward Landler, co-creator of "I Build the Tower: Sam Rodia and the Watts Towers" film.
  - Wendy Rogers Dance Company., undated (Box 30, Folder 19)
    Photocopy of review of "Living Rooms" performance.
  - Weisberger, Barbara., 1985 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    Letter from the director of The Carlisle Project, a Center for Professional Ballet Studies and Choreographic Development.
  - Wenner, Gene., 1975 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    Letter from Rockerfeller Arts in Education Program.
  - Wesleyan University Press., 2003 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    Letters concerning AFS's review of "Belly Dance: Representation, Orientalism and Harmen fantasy" by Shay and Sellers-Young.
  - White, Cuchi., 2002 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    Letter from the photographer. Exhibit brochures in French.
  - Whitehouse, Mary., 1983, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    Letter about AFS's future presentation at The Mary Starks Whitehouse Institute. Authentic Movement Institute brochure.
  - Whitfield, D. Christina., undated (Box 30, Folder 25)
    Christmas card from ex-WAC student.
  - Whitney, John., 1996 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    Photocopy of list of Whitney's films.
  - Whitney Museum., 2008-2009 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    Letter about the Buckminster Fuller exhibit "Starting with the Universe" and AFS speech delivered. "Buckminster Fuller Symposium" at Cooper Union program.
  - Wigman, Mary., 1995-2004 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    Princeton Book Company royalties letter. "Footnotes on the Life of a Dancer: Mary Wigman" by Masami Kuni. Oct./Nov. 2000, summer 2003, winter/spring 2005 "Dance Horizons Videos" catalog.
  - Williams, Drid (1 of 2)., 1974-1984 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    Correspondence with the past UCLA student. Photocopy of draft of thesis "The Role of Movement in Selected Symbolic Systems." "Chomskyan Linguistics and Dance." "Why Make a Distinction Between 'Semiology' and 'Semasiology'?" "The Brides of Christ." "Deep Structures of the Dance." Open letter to Suzanne, Associate Editor of "Dance Encyclopedia."
  - Williams, Drid (2 of 2)., 1974-1983 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    "Semasiology: A semantic anthropological view of human movements and actions." Correspondence concerning job applications. CV. "An Exercise in Applied Personal Anthropology." Draft of 1982 "Presentation for the SEM Conference." Draft of "(Non) Anthropologists, the Dance and Human Movement." "Some Definitional Problems: The dance." "The Dance Experience and Language." "What Are People Doing When They Dance?"
  - Wilson, Robert., 1986 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    "Robert Wilson's 'Alcestis': A classic for the '80s" newsclipping.
  - Wimmer, Shirley., 1972-1994 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    Notice of death and obituary. Correspondence about ethnic dance.
  - Winter, Ethel N., 2008 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    Letter from the Martha Hills Dance Fund.
  - Wohlstetter, Albert., 1997 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    Memorial program and obituary of nuclear strategy expert.
  - Wolf, Herman (1 of 2)., 1996-2004 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    Correspondence and drafts of pages concerning his book about Buckminster Fuller "Bucky's Miracles." 90th birthday celebration program. Recording of McLuhan's "The Medium is the Message." Articles about the "New Geodesic Ball to Fall at Times Square." Obituary.
  - Wolf, Herman (2 of 2)., 1996-2005 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    Correspondence and a bound 1996 draft of his book about Buckminster Fuller "Bucky's Miracles." 1986 insert "Bridgeport Salutes Liberty." 1996 publications "6- Town News" from Bridgeport, Connecticut.
  - Wolff, Mary K., 1987 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    CV. Correspondence concerning job search.
  - Wolz, Carl., 2002 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    Obituaries. CV.
  - Wong, Yen Lu., 1977-1979 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    NEH proposal "The Chinese Cultural Experience in America: An approach through the movement arts." "Yen Lu Wong: A new force in the wings." CV. "Identity, Diversity and the Art of Movement." "Golden Mountain: A choreographer speaks of search and discovery." "Cokes and Fortune Cookies." Correspondence and articles concerning study of Chinese immigrant arts.
  - World Dance Alliance (WDA)., 1993-2003 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    1997 General Assembly record of proceedings. By-laws and drafts of assembly schedules. 1993 First General Assembly of the Americas Center program. New York City Ballet's 1993 Balanchine Celebration program. Some CORD meetings information 1993-1995. Summer, fall, winter 2001 and fall 2002 of WDA newsletters "Channels, Canales." 2003 general assembly registration form.
  - Wright, Frank Lloyd., 1994-1996 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    "Wright Way: The legacy of organic architecture as practice by Eric Lloyd Wright, Lloyd Wright. Frank Lloyd Wright" brochure. March 1994 "New Yorker" article. Letter from Edgar Tafel.
  - Yepez, Lucila., 1987 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    Letter of reference.
  - Yodh, Medha B., 2007 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    Memorial program and obituaries.
  - Yonkers, Dolores., 1997 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    AFS letter to secure a meeting between Yonkers and Valerie Shaaraf Justin.
  - Young, L. Martina., 2007 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    Note concerning chapters for graduate work.
  - Youngblood, Gene., 2000 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    Email concerning Youngblood lecture "Media Arts and Media Politics in the New Millennium."
  - Youngstedt, Scott M., 1990-1992 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    Dissertation proposal about the Hausa. Reports from Niger.
  - Yurick, Loretta A., 1984-1991 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    Dance Theatre of Ireland brochure. Photocopies of correspondence about the work of Yurick and Robert Connor. Photocopies of photos.
  - Zeitlin, Harriet., 1997 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    Letter of recommendation for Guggenheim Fellowship.
  - Zendora, Nancy., 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    Kealiinohomodu Research proposal. CV. Articles about Zendora.
  - Oral History Correspondence., 1994 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    Correspondence relating to the Oral History Project of AFS conducted by Richard Candida Smith.
  - AFS Oral History (1 of 3)., 1993 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    Biographical summary. February 16, 1993 transcribed interview pages 1 through 210.
  - AFS Oral History (2 of 3)., 1993 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    February 16, 1993 transcribed interview pages 211 through 375.
  - AFS Oral History (3 of 3)., 1993 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    February 16, 1993 transcribed interview pages 376 through 554.
- UCLA Administrative Papers., 1960-2010
  This series is focused on the administrative papers of AFS, an early Chair of UCLA's Dance Department (1974-1980, Spring 1984, and 1990-1991), founding Coordinator/Chair for the Ethnic Arts cum World Arts and Cultures Program (1972-1983), Chair of the Faculty of the School of Arts (1989-1991), and Professor of Dance / Dance Ethnology. The files include Snyder's academic papers, university newsletters, UCLA committee and faculty meeting minutes, and professional correspondence that addresses the development of the dance and WAC programs, meeting logistics, and resolutions of committee issues. There is a merging of Snyder's professional and personal endeavors.
  - Aboriginal Arts of Australia., 1980 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Correspondence with Spider Kedelsky about proposed Aboriginal Arts of Australia program.
  - Academic Personnel-Ad Hoc Committee., 1981 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    Handwritten commentary on two committee decisions.
  - Advisors., 1985-1991 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    Meeting agenda. Literature about performing as a graduate, undergraduate, or international student adviser.
  - African Area Studies Program., 1988-1990 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    Proposal for established core course in program. 1988 meeting notes.
  - African Film Project., 1957-1979 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    Correspondence with Robert Cancel of the African Media Center at Michigan State University. Synopses of films about African arts from 1957 to 1977 including the Mbira series.
  - African Studies Center., 1976-1979 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    "African Humanities Institute: Yoruba Program." Proposals for African videotape and institutes programs. Flyer for "Contexts of African Dance."
  - African Studies Association (ASA)., 1974-1979 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    1975 "Self-Review of the M.A. Degree Program in African Area Studies." Correspondence concerning programming with African Studies.
  - Alumni., 1991 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    "1991 Alumni Awards Ceremony Program."
  - American Indian Studies Center (AISC) 1976-1977. (Box 34, Folder 9)
    Proposal for interdepartmental graduate M.A. degree program in American Indian Studies at UCLA.
  - American Indian Studies Center (AISC) 1980. (Box 34, Folder 10)
    "Master of Arts Proposal in American Indian Studies" and inserts. Jill Drayson Sweet CV.
  - American Indian Studies Center (AISC) 1981-1985. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    Interdepartmental core faculty meeting agendas. List of approved courses for fall 1984 MA program. "Five Year Review-AY 1979-1984" of AISC and correspondence. Directives and comments about Dance Department's support of AISC program, 1978. "Graduate Program Goals, Rationale, and Structure." "UCLA American Indian Studies Graduate Student Handbook 1984-1985."
  - American Indian Studies Center (AISC) 1985-1986 (1 of 2). (Box 35, Folder 2)
    Faculty Advisory Committee (FAC) meeting notes and minutes. AISC library correspondence and Willard Rhodes donation list. Newsclipping about establishment of American Indian Chair at UC Riverside. Oandasan grievance letter. Research grant application and correspondence.
  - American Indian Studies Center (AISC) 1985-1986 (2 of 2). (Box 35, Folder 3)